<xml>
	<xml redniBroj="1">1-TAP anywhere to JUMP
	     2-TAP and HOLD to JUMP HIGHER</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="2">When in the AIR you can TAP and HOLD to GLIDE slowly to the ground</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="3">Jump on enemies' heads to knock'em out.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="4">Avoid spikes, plants and TNT barrels if you want to live!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="5">Want to keep playing? Spend one of your bananas to continue running.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="6">No bananas left? Shop is the right place for you!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="7">Bobo's not handsome enough? You can style him up in the Customize section.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="8">Don't miss Tips and Tricks in the Loading Screen, they can be useful.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="9">You can earn some extra coins by inviting your facebook friends to play.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="10">Land on a mushroom for an extra boost!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="11">SWIPE DOWN at great heights to perform a deadly super drop!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="12">Play bonus levels to earn great rewards!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="13">Short of coins? Try out FREE COINS section.</xml>
	<!--<xml redniBroj="14">Jump on vine to swing. Swipe down while swinging to quickly get down.</xml>-->
	<xml redniBroj="15">Bananas are very rare, try not to miss them!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="16">Use Double Coins power-up to get double coins on level.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="17">With Coins Magnet power-up you can collect nearby coins, but it won't last forever.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="18">Shield power-up can protect you from any enemy, but only once!</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="19">Keep an eye on the number of stars on each island.</xml>
	<!--<xml redniBroj="20">Stuck on a difficult mission? Do not give up easily and try again!</xml>-->
	<!--<xml redniBroj="21">Bobo once ate 50 bananas for breakfast. He was happy.</xml>-->
	<!--<xml redniBroj="22">Baboons and gorillas used to live in harmony. Good times.</xml>-->
	<xml redniBroj="23">Watch out for this fellow! His boomerang is dangerous.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="24">Spear gorillas belong to elite squad of gorilla soldiers but you can still smack them on their big head.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="25">Piranha plant. Steady. Hungry. Dangerous.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="26">Visit leaderboard to see your and your friends' standings.</xml>
	<xml redniBroj="27">Share your adventures and brag to your friends.</xml>
	<!--<xml redniBroj="28">Dress up Bobo and share his looks!</xml>-->
	<!--<xml redniBroj="29">Wasting some time...</xml>-->
</xml>